export default {
    PHP: {
        front: '#FFFFFF',
        back: '#4F5D95'
    },
    JavaScript: {
        front: '#000000',
        back: '#F1E05A'
    },
    HTML: {
        front: '#FFFFFF',
        back: '#E34C26'
    },
    Python: {
        front: '#FFFFFF',
        back: '#3572A5'
    },
    TSQL: {
        front: '#000000',
        back: '#DAD8D8'
    },
    Gherkin: {
        front: '#FFFFFF',
        back: '#5B2063'
    },
    Go: {
        front: '#FFFFFF',
        back: '#00ADD8'
    },
    Makefile: {
        front: '#FFFFFF',
        back: '#427819'
    },
    Shell: {
        front: '#000000',
        back: '#89E051'
    },
    CSS: {
        front: '#FFFFFF',
        back: '#563D7C'
    },
    XSLT: {
        front: '#000000',
        back: '#EB8CEB'
    }
};
